<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="53">
	<author>Balu</author>
	<title>
		<en>AutoDrive</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[This mod can be used to create a network of routes for vehicles to drive autonomously. Once setup you can tell a tractor which is standing anywhere close to the network to drive to any point, such as the shop, field 1 or to a sell point.

Changelog 1.1.0.8:
FIX [BUG] Middle click snaps waypoint to vehicle in edit mode #1723

ADDED support auger wagon over-/unloading to trailer
- vehicle will slow down to 5km/h at setting maxTriggerDistance before target and open pipe
- unload to all trailers on the way to target
- if not unloaded complete, drive to target and wait to be unloaded somehow (as in the past)
ADDED retry unload at trigger
- unloader wil stay at trigger and retry to unload only if trigger is not already 100% full when reaching the trigger
- Limitation: if trigger is 100% full when reaching the unload trigger, vehicle continue to destination  (LS engine limitation) and wait to unload somehow (as in the past)
ADDED overload to fillable (liquids) trailer
ADDED adExportRoutesAsExternalMod console command to create route export as a mod, which could be used by other users / machines on the same map
ADDED Editormode (red bubbles): start auto-connection on selected waypoint with LCTRL key hold
ADDED CP park vehicle now use the park position from selected vehicle/attachment

ADDED new key+mouse combination to set/delete P destination
left-mouse -> no change, will send vehicle to park in every AD Mode
NEW:
Editormode (red bubbles) + RCTRL + right-mouse on P -> set/override P with 1st destination in HUD
Editormode (red bubbles) + RALT + right-mouse on P -> delete park destination

TWEAK Changed calculation of reverse distance and speed after harvester unloading
TWEAK improved waypoint movement, do not glitch into / below visible ground
TWEAK removed message harvester unloader could not reach harvester as it will restart finding the harvester after some time itself
TWEAK several translation updates
TWEAK fixed simultaneous recording on MP
TWEAK refuel DEF and ELECTRIC at triggers where DEF, ELECTRIC or DIESEL are available
TWEAK path finding:
setting avoidFruit works now also outside of field borders to avoid driving through a field with fruit to the next network waypoint if possible
setting pathFinderTime should only be slightly increased if avoidFruit is not proper working with sufficient headland is available (~20+ m), high value will increase the calculation time
3 fallback scenario will automatic take effect: 
First fallback (setting restrictToField is enabled) will extend the "field border" by ~30+ meters around the field pathfinding was started - extend the room for vehicle to find a path
Second fallback (setting restrictToField is enabled) will deactivate all field border restrictions
Third fallback (setting avoidFruit is enabled) will disable fruit avoid automatically if no path was found
If fallbacks will not succeed to find a path you will get the message path not found.
Overall performance improvement to reduce calculation time and FPS drops. Synchronize calculation time between multiple vehicles with ongoing path calculation.
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[Dieser Mod erlaubt es ein Netzwerk von Routen aufzuzeichnen, um dann ein Fahrzeug von jedem beliebigen Punkt zu speziell definierten Zielen, wie zum Beispiel der eigenen Farm, Feld 1 oder auch zu jedem Verkaufspunkt fahren zu lassen.

Changelog 1.1.0.8:
FIX [BUG] Mittlerer Klick rastet Wegpunkt an Fahrzeug im Bearbeitungsmodus ein #1723

ADDED Unterstützung Schneckenwagen über-/abladen auf Anhänger
- Fahrzeug wird bei Einstellung maxTriggerDistance vor dem Ziel auf 5km/h verlangsamt und öffnet Rohr
- entlade auf alle Anhänger auf dem Weg zum Ziel
- wenn nicht vollständig entladen, zum Ziel fahren und warten, um irgendwie entladen zu werden (wie in der Vergangenheit)
ADDED retry unload at trigger
- Entlader bleibt am Trigger und versucht nur dann erneut zu entladen, wenn der Trigger bei Erreichen des Triggers nicht bereits 100% voll ist
- Einschränkung: wenn der Trigger bei Erreichen des Entlade-Triggers 100% voll ist, fährt das Fahrzeug weiter zum Ziel (LS-Einschränkung) und wartet, um irgendwie zu entladen (wie in der Vergangenheit)
ADDED überladen in (Flüssigkeits-) Anhänger
ADDED adExportRoutesAsExternalMod Konsolenbefehl, um einen Routenexport als Mod zu erstellen, der von anderen Benutzern / Maschinen auf der gleichen Map verwendet werden kann
ADDED Editormode (rote Punkte): Autoverbindung auf ausgewählten Wegpunkt mit LCTRL-Tastendruck starten
ADDED CP: Park Fahrzeug verwendet jetzt die Parkposition vom ausgewählten Fahrzeug/Anbaugerät

ADDED neue Taste+Maus-Kombination zum Setzen/Löschen von P-Zielen
linke-Maus -> keine Änderung, schickt Fahrzeug in jedem AD-Modus zum Parken
NEU:
Editormode (rote Punkte) + RCTRL + rechte Maustaste auf P -> P mit 1. Ziel im HUD setzen/überschreiben
Editormodus (rote Punkte) + RALT + rechte Maustaste auf P -> Parkziel löschen

TWEAK Berechnung der Rückwärtsstrecke und Geschwindigkeit nach dem Entladen des Ernters angepasst
TWEAK verbesserte Wegpunkt-Bewegung, glitchen nicht in / unter sichtbaren Boden
TWEAK Meldung kein Weg zu Ernter gefunden entfernt, da er nach einiger Zeit selbst wieder anfängt, den Ernter zu finden
TWEAK mehrere Übersetzungs-Updates
TWEAK gleichzeitige Aufzeichnung auf MP behoben
TWEAK Tanken von DEF und ELECTRIC an Triggern, wo DEF, ELECTRIC oder DIESEL verfügbar sind
TWEAK Wegfindung:
Einstellung Fruchtumfahrung funktioniert jetzt auch außerhalb von Feldgrenzen, um das Durchfahren eines Feldes mit Früchten zum nächsten Wegpunkt möglichst zu vermeiden
Die Einstellung Pfadfindungs-Faktor sollte nur leicht erhöht werden, wenn Fruchtumfahrung nicht richtig funktioniert und genügend Vorgewende vorhanden ist (~20+ m), ein hoher Wert erhöht die Berechnungszeit
3 Fallback-Szenarien werden automatisch wirksam: 
Erster Fallback (Einstellung Pfadplanung begrenzt ist aktiviert) erweitert die "Feldgrenze" um ~30+ Meter um das Feld, in dem die Wegfindung gestartet wurde - erweitert den Raum für das Fahrzeug, einen Weg zu finden
Zweiter Fallback (Einstellung Pfadplanung begrenzt ist aktiviert) deaktiviert alle Feldrandeinschränkungen
Der dritte Fallback (Einstellung Fruchtumfahrung ist aktiviert) deaktiviert die Fruchtumfahrung, wenn kein Pfad gefunden wurde.
Wenn Fallbacks nicht erfolgreich sind, um einen Pfad zu finden, erhalten Sie die Meldung kein Weg gefunden.
Allgemeine Leistungsverbesserung, um die Berechnungszeit und FPS-Einbrüche zu reduzieren. Synchronisierung der Berechnungszeit zwischen mehreren Fahrzeugen bei laufender Pfadberechnung.
]]>
		</de>
		<it>
			<![CDATA[Questa mod può essere usata per creare una rete di percorsi per permettere ai veicoli di guidare autonomamente. Una volta effettuata la configurazione puoi dire a un veicolo di guidare tramite la rete verso un qualsiasi punto, come il negozio, il campo 1 o un punto vendita.

Log delle modifiche 1.1.0.8:
CORRETTO [BUG] Il click centrale aggancia il waypoint al veicolo in modalità modifica #1723

AGGIUNTO supporto carro a coclea per sovraccarico/scarico su rimorchio
- il veicolo rallenterà a 5km/h impostando maxTriggerDistance prima dell'obiettivo e del tubo aperto
- scarica a tutti i rimorchi sulla strada per l'obiettivo
- se non viene scaricato completamente, guida fino all'obiettivo e aspetta di essere scaricato in qualche modo (come in passato)
AGGIUNTO riprovare a scaricare all'innesco
- lo scaricatore rimane all'innesco e riprova a scaricare solo se l'innesco non è già pieno al 100% quando lo raggiunge
- Limitazione: se il trigger è pieno al 100% quando raggiunge il trigger di scarico, il veicolo continua a destinazione (limitazione del motore LS) e aspetta di scaricare in qualche modo (come in passato)
AGGIUNTO sovraccarico al rimorchio riempibile (liquidi)
AGGIUNTO comando console adExportRoutesAsExternalMod per creare l'esportazione del percorso come mod, che potrebbe essere usato da altri utenti / macchine sulla stessa mappa
AGGIUNTO Editormode (bolle rosse): avvia l'autoconnessione sul waypoint selezionato tenendo premuto il tasto LCTRL
AGGIUNTO CP park vehicle ora usa la posizione di parcheggio dal veicolo/attaccamento selezionato

AGGIUNTA nuova combinazione tasto+mouse per impostare/cancellare la destinazione P
left-mouse -> nessun cambiamento, manderà il veicolo a parcheggiare in ogni AD Mode
NUOVO:
Editormode (bolle rosse) + RCTRL + tasto destro del mouse su P -> imposta/esclude P con la prima destinazione nell'HUD
Editormode (bolle rosse) + RALT + tasto destro del mouse su P -> cancella la destinazione del parcheggio

TWEAK Cambiato il calcolo della distanza e della velocità inversa dopo lo scarico della mietitrice
TWEAK migliorato il movimento dei waypoint, non ci sono glitch nel / sotto il terreno visibile
TWEAK rimosso il messaggio che lo scaricatore di mietitrebbie non ha potuto raggiungere la mietitrebbia, in quanto riprenderà a cercare la mietitrebbia dopo qualche tempo
TWEAK diversi aggiornamenti di traduzione
TWEAK fissata la registrazione simultanea su MP
TWEAK rifornimento DEF e ELECTRIC ai trigger dove DEF, ELECTRIC o DIESEL sono disponibili
TWEAK ricerca del percorso:
l'impostazione avoidFruit funziona ora anche al di fuori dei confini del campo per evitare di guidare attraverso un campo con frutta fino al prossimo waypoint della rete, se possibile
l'impostazione pathFinderTime dovrebbe essere solo leggermente aumentata se avoidFruit non funziona correttamente se è disponibile una capezzagna sufficiente (~20+ m), un valore alto aumenterà il tempo di calcolo
3 scenari di fallback avranno effetto automatico: 
Il primo fallback (l'impostazione restrictToField è abilitata) estenderà il "confine del campo" di ~30+ metri intorno al campo in cui è stato avviato il pathfinding - estendendo lo spazio per il veicolo per trovare un percorso
Il secondo fallback (impostando restrictToField è abilitato) disattiverà tutte le restrizioni del confine del campo
Il terzo fallback (l'impostazione avoidFruit è abilitata) disabiliterà automaticamente l'evitamento della frutta se non è stato trovato alcun percorso
Se i fallback non riusciranno a trovare un percorso si otterrà il messaggio percorso non trovato.
Miglioramento generale delle prestazioni per ridurre il tempo di calcolo e i cali di FPS. Sincronizzare il tempo di calcolo tra più veicoli con il calcolo del percorso in corso.

]]>
		</it>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[Ce mod peut être utilisé pour créer un réseau de routes permettant aux véhicules de conduire de manière autonome. Une fois la configuration effectuée, vous pouvez indiquer à un tracteur situé près du réseau de se rendre à n’importe quel point, tel que le magasin, le champ 1 ou un point de vente.
Créer, ajouter, modifier, supprimer vos routes ou points de destination à l'aide de l'éditeur intégré très pratique !
Différents modes d'utilisation ont été ajoutés depuis les premières versions, et peuvent être combinés à l'utilisation du bien connu "Courseplay".

Changelog 1.1.0.8:
CORRECTION [BUG] Le clic du milieu fixe le point de cheminement vers le véhicule en mode d'édition #1723

AJOUTER un soutien au surchargement/déchargement du wagon à vis sans fin sur la remorque
- le véhicule ralentira à 5km/h à la distance de déclenchement maximale avant la cible et le tuyau ouvert
- décharger à toutes les remorques en route vers la cible
- si le déchargement n'est pas complet, se rendre à la cible et attendre d'être déchargé d'une manière ou d'une autre (comme par le passé)
AJOUTER une nouvelle tentative de déchargement au moment du déclenchement
- le déchargeur restera sur le déclencheur et n'essaiera à nouveau de décharger que si le déclencheur n'est pas déjà plein à 100% lorsqu'il atteint le déclencheur
- Limitation : si le déclencheur est plein à 100 % lorsqu'il atteint le déclencheur de déchargement, le véhicule continue vers sa destination (limitation du moteur LS) et attend pour décharger d'une manière ou d'une autre (comme par le passé)
AJOUTER une surcharge à la remorque (liquide) remplissable
Ajout de la commande adExportRoutesAsExternalMod en console pour créer l'exportation de routes sous forme de mod, qui pourrait être utilisé par d'autres utilisateurs / machines sur la même carte
ADDED Editormode (bulles rouges) : démarrage de l'auto-connexion sur le point de passage sélectionné avec maintien de la touche LCTRL
AJOUTÉ CP véhicule de parc utiliser maintenant la position de parc du véhicule/attachement sélectionné

AJOUTER une nouvelle combinaison clé+souris pour définir/supprimer la destination P
souris de gauche -> pas de changement, enverra le véhicule se garer dans tous les modes AD
NOUVEAU :
Mode éditeur (bulles rouges) + RCTRL + souris droite sur P -> régler/supprimer P avec 1ère destination dans le HUD
Mode éditeur (bulles rouges) + RALT + souris droite sur P -> supprimer la destination du parc

TWEAK Modification du calcul de la distance et de la vitesse de recul après le déchargement de la récolteuse
TWEAK : amélioration du mouvement des points de cheminement, ne pas se glisser dans le sol visible
TWEAK a supprimé le message "harvester unloader" (déchargeur de la moissonneuse) qui n'a pas pu atteindre la moissonneuse car il recommencera à la trouver lui-même après un certain temps
TWEAK plusieurs mises à jour de traduction
TWEAK a fixé l'enregistrement simultané sur MP
TWEAK fait le plein de DEF et d'ELECTRIC aux points de déclenchement où le DEF, l'ELECTRIC ou le DIESEL sont disponibles
TWEAK recherche de chemin :
setting avoidFruit travaille maintenant aussi en dehors des frontières des champs pour éviter de traverser un champ avec des fruits jusqu'au prochain point de cheminement du réseau si possible
le réglage de pathFinderTime ne doit être que légèrement augmenté si avoidFruit ne fonctionne pas correctement avec un promontoire suffisant (~20+ m), une valeur élevée augmentera le temps de calcul
Le scénario de repli 3 prendra automatiquement effet : 
Le premier scénario de repli (le paramètre restrictToField est activé) prolongera la "frontière du champ" de plus de 30 mètres autour du champ où la recherche de chemin a été lancée.
La deuxième solution (le paramètre restrictToField est activé) désactivera toutes les restrictions aux frontières des champs
Troisième repli (le paramètre avoidFruit est activé) qui désactivera automatiquement l'évitement des fruits si aucun chemin n'a été trouvé
Si les repliements ne parviennent pas à trouver un chemin, vous obtiendrez le chemin de message non trouvé.
Amélioration globale des performances pour réduire le temps de calcul et les chutes de FPS. Synchroniser le temps de calcul entre plusieurs véhicules avec le calcul du chemin en cours.

]]>
		</fr>
		<es>
			<![CDATA[Este mod se utiliza para crear una red de rutas y permitir que los vehículos conduzcan de forma autónoma. Una vez configurado, puede ordenar a un tractor, cercano a la red, que conduzca a cualquier meta definida, como la tienda, el campo 1 o un punto de venta.]]>
		</es>
		<ru>
			<![CDATA[Этот мод может быть использован для создания сети маршрутов для транспортных средств для автономного вождения. После настройки вы можете указать трактору, стоящему где-угодно рядом с сетью, проехать в любую точку, например, в магазин, поле №1 или в точку продажи.]]>
		</ru>
	</description>
	<version>1.1.0.9</version>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="register.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />

	<actions>
		<action name="ADToggleMouse" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADToggleHud" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADEnDisable" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectTarget" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousTarget" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectTargetUnload" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousTargetUnload" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADActivateDebug" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugSelectNeighbor" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugChangeNeighbor" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugCreateConnection" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugCreateMapMarker" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugDeleteWayPoint" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugDeleteDestination" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectNextFillType" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousFillType" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADRecord" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_routes_manager" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSilomode" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADOpenGUI" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADCallDriver" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADGoToVehicle" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADNameDriver" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADIncLoopCounter" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADRenameMapMarker" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSwapTargets" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_open_notification_history" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_continue" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADParkVehicle" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_devAction" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
	</actions>

	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADToggleHud">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_KP_0" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_17" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADOpenGUI">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_0" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_16" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADToggleMouse">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_MIDDLE" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="3" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_19" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADEnDisable">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_up" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_17" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectTarget">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_right" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_18" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousTarget">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_left" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_20" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectTargetUnload">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_3+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousTargetUnload">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_3-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADActivateDebug">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_11" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugSelectNeighbor">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_9" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugChangeNeighbor">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_4-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugCreateConnection">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_12" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectNextFillType">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_o" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_2-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousFillType">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_4" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_2+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADRecord">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_3" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AD_routes_manager">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_1" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSilomode">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_4+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AD_open_notification_history">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_m" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
</modDesc>
