<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="53">
	<author>Balu</author>
	<title>
		<en>AutoDrive</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[This mod can be used to create a network of routes for vehicles to drive autonomously. Once setup you can tell a tractor which is standing anywhere close to the network to drive to any point, such as the shop, field 1 or to a sell point.

Changelog 1.1.1.0:
FIX collision handling caused unloader to stop-and-go behind chopper
FIX multiple trailer unload harvester 

ADDED combine open pipe when precall-level is reached
ADDED CP interface for co-operation with newer CP versions
ADDED experimental features:
- blue Line Route Finder: default OFF, enable if AD could not find a route via multiple passes dark blue connections, feedback if issues occure
- detect Gras Field: default ON, harvester will detect gras field and assign the correct side to unloader

TWEAK improved liquid overload:
- only start loading in silo-trigger-range and if trigger is found
TWEAK harvester - unloader - co-operation:
- increased reverse distance for unloader
- CP harvester should wait some seconds while unloader is driving reverse
TWEAK rework park destination:
- MP synchronized
- all destinations handled now internally in vehicles.xml in tag AutoDriveVehicleData parkDestination, AD will update automatical
TWEAK debug road network:
- performance optimisation, especial when deactivating route network debug
- changed: known markers for open / dead route ends now named with "1_..."
- new: route network with connections AD might not use due to issues named "2_...", i.e. reverse section (light blue) within one-way direction (green)
TWEAK reset AD modes if started should fix/avoid unusual behaviour(s)
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[Dieser Mod erlaubt es ein Netzwerk von Routen aufzuzeichnen, um dann ein Fahrzeug von jedem beliebigen Punkt zu speziell definierten Zielen, wie zum Beispiel der eigenen Farm, Feld 1 oder auch zu jedem Verkaufspunkt fahren zu lassen.

Changelog 1.1.1.0:
FIX Kollisionsbehandlung führte zu Stop-and-Go des Entladers hinter dem Häcksler
FIX mehrere Anhänger entladen Mähdrescher 

ADDED Mähdrescher fährt Rohr bei Erreichen des eingestellten Füllstandes aus
ADDED CP-Schnittstelle für die Zusammenarbeit mit neueren CP-Versionen aktualisiert
ADDED experimentelle Funktionen:
- blue Line Route Finder: standardmäßig AUS, aktivieren, wenn AD über mehrere Durchgänge keine Route finden konnte für dunkelblaue Verbindungen, Rückmeldung, wenn Probleme auftreten
- Grasfeld erkennen: standardmäßig EIN, Ernter erkennen Grasfeld und weisen dem Entlader die richtige Seite zu

TWEAK verbesserte Flüssigkeitsüberladung:
- Start der Beladung nur im Silo-Trigger-Bereich und wenn Trigger gefunden wird
TWEAK Mähdrescher - Ablader - Zusammenarbeit:
- Rückwärtsstrecke für Ablader erhöht
- CP Harvester sollte einige Sekunden warten, während der Entlader rückwärts fährt
TWEAK Überarbeitete Parkziel-Zuweisung:
- MP synchronisiert
- alle Ziele werden jetzt intern in vehicles.xml im Tag AutoDriveVehicleData parkDestination behandelt, wird von AD automatisch aktualisiert
TWEAK Debuggen Straßennetz:
- Performance-Optimierung, insbesondere bei Deaktivierung von Routennetz-Debug
- geändert: bekannte Marker für offene / tote Routenenden jetzt mit "1_..." benannt
- neu: Streckennetz mit Verbindungen, die AD wegen Problemen nicht verwenden könnte werden mit "2_..." benannt, z.B. Rückwärtsstrecke (hellblau) in Einbahnrichtung (grün)
TWEAK Reset der AD-Modi sollte ungewöhnliche(s) Verhalten beheben/verhindern
]]>
		</de>
		<it>
			<![CDATA[Questa mod può essere usata per creare una rete di percorsi per permettere ai veicoli di guidare autonomamente. Una volta effettuata la configurazione puoi dire a un veicolo di guidare tramite la rete verso un qualsiasi punto, come il negozio, il campo 1 o un punto vendita.

Log delle modifiche 1.1.1.0:
FIX la gestione delle collisioni causava lo stop-and-go dello scaricatore dietro l'elicottero
FIX scarico di più rimorchi della mietitrebbia 

AGGIUNTO tubo di apertura della mietitrebbia quando viene raggiunto il livello di precarico
AGGIUNTA interfaccia CP per la cooperazione con le versioni CP più recenti
AGGIUNTA funzionalità sperimentale:
- blue Line Route Finder: default OFF, abilitare se AD non è riuscito a trovare un percorso attraverso più passaggi connessioni blu scuro, feedback se si verificano problemi
- rilevare campo Gras: default ON, la mietitrice rileverà il campo Gras e assegnerà il lato corretto allo scaricatore

TWEAK migliorato sovraccarico liquidi:
- inizia a caricare solo nel campo silo-trigger e se viene trovato il trigger
TWEAK cooperazione tra mietitrice e scaricatore:
- aumento della distanza inversa per lo scaricatore
- CP harvester dovrebbe aspettare alcuni secondi mentre lo scaricatore guida in retromarcia
TWEAK rielaborazione destinazione parco:
- MP sincronizzato
- tutte le destinazioni gestite ora internamente in vehicles.xml nel tag AutoDriveVehicleData parkDestination, AD si aggiornerà automaticamente
TWEAK debug rete stradale:
- ottimizzazione delle prestazioni, specialmente quando si disattiva il debug della rete stradale
- cambiato: i marcatori noti per i terminali di percorso aperti / morti ora sono nominati con "1_..."
- nuovo: rete stradale con connessioni che AD potrebbe non utilizzare a causa di problemi denominata "2_...", cioè sezione inversa (blu chiaro) all'interno di una direzione a senso unico (verde)
TWEAK ripristina le modalità AD se avviato dovrebbe risolvere/evitare comportamenti insoliti

Tradotto con www.DeepL.com/Translator (versione gratuita)
]]>
		</it>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[Ce mod peut être utilisé pour créer un réseau de routes permettant aux véhicules de conduire de manière autonome. Une fois la configuration effectuée, vous pouvez indiquer à un tracteur situé près du réseau de se rendre à n’importe quel point, tel que le magasin, le champ 1 ou un point de vente.
Créer, ajouter, modifier, supprimer vos routes ou points de destination à l'aide de l'éditeur intégré très pratique !
Différents modes d'utilisation ont été ajoutés depuis les premières versions, et peuvent être combinés à l'utilisation du bien connu "Courseplay".

Changelog 1.1.1.0:
Correction de la gestion des collisions qui provoquait l'arrêt et le déplacement du déchargeur derrière l'hélico.
FIXE le déchargement de plusieurs remorques sur la moissonneuse 

Ajout d'un tuyau d'ouverture de la moissonneuse-batteuse lorsque le niveau de précaution est atteint.
Ajout d'une interface CP pour coopérer avec les nouvelles versions du CP.
Ajout de fonctionnalités expérimentales :
- blue Line Route Finder : par défaut OFF, activer si AD n'a pas pu trouver une route via des connexions bleu foncé à passages multiples, feedback si des problèmes surviennent
- detect Gras Field : ON par défaut, la moissonneuse détectera le champ de graminées et assignera le bon côté au déchargeur.

TWEAK a amélioré la surcharge de liquide :
- ne commence le chargement que dans la zone de déclenchement du silo et si le déclencheur est trouvé.
TWEAK coopération moissonneuse - déchargeur :
- augmentation de la distance de recul du déchargeur
- La moissonneuse CP doit attendre quelques secondes pendant que le déchargeur fait marche arrière.
TWEAK destination du parc de retraitement :
- MP synchronisé
- toutes les destinations sont maintenant gérées en interne dans vehicles.xml dans le tag AutoDriveVehicleData parkDestination, AD sera mis à jour automatiquement
TWEAK déboguer le réseau routier :
- optimisation des performances, en particulier lors de la désactivation du débogage du réseau routier
- modifié : les marqueurs connus pour les fins de route ouvertes / mortes sont maintenant nommés avec "1_...".
- nouveau : réseau routier avec des connexions que AD pourrait ne pas utiliser en raison de problèmes nommés "2_...", c.-à-d. section inverse (bleu clair) dans un sens unique (vert)
TWEAK réinitialise les modes AD s'ils sont lancés, ce qui devrait corriger/éviter les comportements inhabituels.

Traduit avec www.DeepL.com/Translator (version gratuite)
]]>
		</fr>
		<es>
			<![CDATA[Este mod se utiliza para crear una red de rutas y permitir que los vehículos conduzcan de forma autónoma. Una vez configurado, puede ordenar a un tractor, cercano a la red, que conduzca a cualquier meta definida, como la tienda, el campo 1 o un punto de venta.]]>
		</es>
		<ru>
			<![CDATA[Этот мод может быть использован для создания сети маршрутов для транспортных средств для автономного вождения. После настройки вы можете указать трактору, стоящему где-угодно рядом с сетью, проехать в любую точку, например, в магазин, поле №1 или в точку продажи.]]>
		</ru>
	</description>
	<version>1.1.1.0</version>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="register.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />

	<actions>
		<action name="ADToggleMouse" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADToggleHud" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADEnDisable" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectTarget" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousTarget" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectTargetUnload" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousTargetUnload" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADActivateDebug" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugSelectNeighbor" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugChangeNeighbor" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugCreateConnection" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugCreateMapMarker" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugDeleteWayPoint" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADDebugDeleteDestination" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectNextFillType" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSelectPreviousFillType" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADRecord" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_routes_manager" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSilomode" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADOpenGUI" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADCallDriver" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADGoToVehicle" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADNameDriver" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADIncLoopCounter" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADRenameMapMarker" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADSwapTargets" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_open_notification_history" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_continue" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="ADParkVehicle" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="AD_devAction" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
	</actions>

	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADToggleHud">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_KP_0" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_17" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADOpenGUI">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_0" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_16" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADToggleMouse">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_MIDDLE" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="3" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_19" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADEnDisable">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_up" axisComponent="+" inputComponent="+" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_17" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectTarget">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_right" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_18" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousTarget">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_left" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_20" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectTargetUnload">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_3+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousTargetUnload">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_3-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADActivateDebug">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_11" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugSelectNeighbor">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_9" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugChangeNeighbor">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_4-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADDebugCreateConnection">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_12" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectNextFillType">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_o" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_2-" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSelectPreviousFillType">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_4" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_2+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADRecord">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_3" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AD_routes_manager">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_KP_1" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="ADSilomode">
			<binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 AXIS_4+" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="AD_open_notification_history">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lalt KEY_m" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
</modDesc>
